hello everyone this is ey on ey censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is the 6th of February
2024 this is a book review on my latest
book that's available now on Amazon soon
it will be available on Barnes &
Noble it's called gaslighting wokeism
infiltrates the Bible Supernatural Bible
changes this small is 5.75 in x 6 in
covers over
400 King James Bible verses that have
been
perverted as well as other verses from
other
translations we're seeing lying signs
and wonders happen right now across
translations across languages across the
Earth and I've been covering these
nefarious Wicked changes since 2016 on
YouTube warning the church anyone who
has ears to hear and eyes to see what's
happening to script anyone who knows the
shepherd's voice because there is a
different voice that's coming through
scripture preparing the way for the
Antichrist it's absolutely diabolical
and it is crazy and it's absolutely true
let me go ahead and show you this on
Amazon this is the book review on Amazon
you can buy it today in
paperback essentially brothers and
sisters Bible prophecy is happening
obviously we know that it's been
happening but we are seeing lying signs
and wonders happen right now we were
warned about this in 2 Thessalonians 2
we are also warned that when the
Antichrist comes upon the Earth he will
deceive the world that he is God and
there will be a great falling away and
this is happening today because the
Antichrist is rising in scripture
pretending that he is God if you have
eyes to see if you have ears to hear
here you will know what I'm talking
about the Bible is allog together a
different book we have new words words
erased new
doctrine
um punctuation and grammar errors
emoticons new people spelling errors all
throughout the Bible today and it's
absolutely crazy and it's absolutely
true how are they doing this black magic
witchcraft potentially I believe through
frequencies I'm not really sure but what
I do know is that our bibles are
changing and it's
self-evident let me go ahead and show
you some examples of what I have in this
small book 1st Samuel 16:20 and Jesse
took an ass Laden with bread and a
bottle of wine and a kid and sent them
by David his son unto Saul 1st Samuel 19
24 and he stripped off his clothes also
and prophesied before Samuel in like
Manner and lay down naked all that day
and all that night wherefore they say is
Saul also among the
prophets I'll continue showing you some
more this is 1 Corinthians
15:49 as we have borne the image of the
earthy we shall also bear the image of
the
Heavenly in 1 Corinthians 158 in the
Darby Bible this a Catholic Bible it
says this today and last of all as to an
abortion he appeared to me also and yes
with those little
asteris 1 Corinthians 16:13 in the King
James Bible watch ye stand firm excuse
me stand fast in the faith quit you like
men be
strong 1 Corinthians 4:11 even into this
present hour we both hunger and thirst
and are naked and are buffeted and have
no certain Dwelling
Place 1 John 3:12 not as Cain who was of
that Wicked one and slew his brother and
wherefore slew he
him because his own Works were evil and
his brothers
righteous First Kings 1:21 otherwise it
shall come to pass when my Lord the king
shall sleep with his
fathers that I and my son Solomon shall
be counted
offenders 1 John 11:16 for 6 months did
joab remain there with all Israel until
he had cut off every male in
Edom with a smiley face
amoon and on and on it goes I'll read
one more to you 1 Kings 12:10 says this
today and the young men that were grown
up with him spake unto him saying thus
sh thou speak unto this people and spake
unto thee saying thy father made our
yoke heavy but Thou made it lighter unto
us thus shalt thou say unto them my
little finger shall be thicker than my
father's
loins I just read several altered
scripture verses that have woke ideology
embedded into it with pronouns new
words and so forth and it's the intended
purpose of this is to deceive the
church it's so obvious that we are
seeing these diabolical Chang in
scripture preparing way for the
Antichrist when it comes to
wokeism it's absolutely clear that this
ideology is
diabolical it's intent upon social
re-engineering leading to the erosion of
conservative values Christian values and
the great falling away the Bible is
being Rewritten in real
time to deceive the church to worship
the
Antichrist and this of course was proph
prophesied in Scripture that there would
be a great falling
away this book is filled with scripture
verses that anyone who has ears to hear
anyone who has eyes to see should
discern the errors and you may need to
stop and think ask the Holy Spirit of
course always to lead and guide you in
all
righteousness ask the Holy Spirit to
show you what I'm trying to show
you I have to create
this book in a creative
way and trusting that the Holy Spirit
Will Reveal to you what those changes
are in light of the topic of wokeism and
it is such a wicked
ideology it's plainly evident and it's
time to wake up in jesus' name again
this book is available on
Amazon and soon will be available on
Barnes &
Noble thanks everyone I pray Our Father
in heaven will bless you encourage you
strengthen you I pray that the gift of
discernment would be amply supplied to
you and that you would diligently C
search out this matter open up your
Bible pray and fast and seek the Lord
this is a dire importance in this
hour and I'm unrelenting on this topic
because the Bible
changes it's not a SC up it's
obvious the Bible is been
Rewritten to deceive as many Souls as
possible it's time to wake up in Jesus
name